<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>korea on Tolar Town</title>
    <link>https://tolar.town/tags/korea/</link>
    <description>Recent content in korea on Tolar Town</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 17:30:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tolar.town/tags/korea/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>So long, Eastern hempisphere</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/25/jeju-to-atlanta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 17:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/25/jeju-to-atlanta/</guid>
      <description>The South Korean leg of my &amp;lsquo;grand tour&amp;rsquo; has come to an end. I&amp;rsquo;m currently sitting in the Korean Airlines lounge in Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Incheon airport, a little exhausted, yet so grateful &amp;amp; happy that I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to spend the past 6 weeks in California, Australia, &amp;amp; South Korea.
This morning, I was in Jeju, and, in a couple of hours, I will board a flight to Atlanta, where I&amp;rsquo;ll get to spend the next 10 days or so celebrating Thanksgiving and spending time with my family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeju II</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/24/jeju-part-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/24/jeju-part-two/</guid>
      <description>It was a rainy day, so we went and picked up some pizzas and chicken for lunch from Magpie, then we went out for a drive.
We had a delicious dinner in the city of chicken &amp;amp; mushroom dumplings, chicken meatballs, pork charsiu, and noodle soup with fish cake.
Oranges! Me &amp;amp; Ellie Magpie posters Dinner</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeju is dope</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/23/jeju/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 21:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/23/jeju/</guid>
      <description>We started the day in Jeju picking some oranges from their back yard. We went out for an amazing lunch, then stopped by the beach for a bit, followed by a visit to Tiffany &amp;amp; Erik&amp;rsquo;s brewery: Magpie. Tiffany &amp;amp; I ducked out for a bbq dinner.
Orange picking Traditional Korean lunch: beef, fish, pancakes, soup, spicy salad with homemade tofu, plenty of yummy sides. Beach Beach selfie Magpie brewery: Brewed on Jeju, Born in Seoul Magpie brewery Tiffany BBQ dinner</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying from Seoul to Jeju</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/22/seoul-to-jeju/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/22/seoul-to-jeju/</guid>
      <description>I met up with Tiffany&amp;rsquo;s family and flew from Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Gimpo airport down to Jeju, an island off the southern coast of South Korea.
Before doing that, I walked a bit around Namsan park near my hotel.
Views of Seoul from Namsan park Cab to Gimpo airport Asiana flight from Seoul Gimpo to Jeju</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Seoul</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/21/old-seoul/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 22:32:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/21/old-seoul/</guid>
      <description>I returned to Bimbam Cafe this morning, but this time got the quiche lorraine, which was even better than yesterday&amp;rsquo;s breakfast. I met up with Tiffany &amp;amp; fam to go down to the park near the Han river.
This afternoon, I took the bus up to the Jongmyo shrine, which I learned I could not enter without a tour. Unfortunately, the next one was 1½ hours away. So I walked up to the Bukchon Hanok village: a neighborhood of old style residential homes that are still in use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 museums &amp; some food</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/20/seoul-museums/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 22:08:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/20/seoul-museums/</guid>
      <description>My first full day in Seoul! I had a good breakfast at Bimbam Cafe near the hotel, then walked down to the War Memorial of Korea, which encompassed lots of history of Korea, with an emphasis on the Korean War.
I had a yummy sandwich at Casablanca in Itaewon, then met up with Tiffany &amp;amp; fam to see the Gyeongbokgung Palace and the Arario museum.
We had a dope Korean dinner of seafood &amp;amp; veggie pancake, a spicy salad with chestnut jelly, and a creamy noodle soup, along with makgeolli, a Korean rice wine that was yum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul!</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/19/seoul/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/19/seoul/</guid>
      <description>After a long flight from Melbourne with a middle-of-the-night layover in Singapore, I made it to Seoul! I took the KAL (Korean Airlines) Limousine Bus from Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Incheon airport to the Grand Hyatt hotel. The bus was pretty nice, as it does a loop from the airport to major hotels in Seoul, so it&amp;rsquo;s a easy, inexpensive way to efficiently get to the destination.
I was pretty wiped out when I checked in, but I managed to walk down to Full Moon where I had a beef bulgogi meal, complete with various Korean style sides.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
