<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>art on Tolar Town</title>
    <link>https://tolar.town/tags/art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in art on Tolar Town</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 14:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tolar.town/tags/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Street art</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/12/street-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 14:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/12/street-art/</guid>
      <description>I went on a walking tour of street art in Melbourne that I found on Airbnb. Lukas took me and another guest around to see some cool street art, pointed out various different styles, and put it all into context and the culture around the street art scene here. BUT, the highlight is that we got to make our own street art. It was awesome! I was super nervous to start, but it came out way better than I had hoped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day out shopping</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/02/shopping-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 20:12:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/02/shopping-day/</guid>
      <description>It was a slow morning due to quite a bit of ongoing rain outside. I did make it out in the morning all the way across the street to the Saturday market to buy a loaf of sourdough and a coffee (which I then had with some eggs I made at home). I finally left the house for a bit this afternoon to get some lunch and check out some shops that were on my list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A lazy day in Fitzroy</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/01/lazy-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 14:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/01/lazy-day/</guid>
      <description>I was wiped out from traveling back from Tasmania and doing the walking tour last night, so I laid low around the neighborhood, did some laundry, and ordered in for dinner. (And got this blog updated!)
Espresso, Grace Café Mushrooms on toast, Grace Café Brunswick Street building Fried chicken sandwich, Industry Beans</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A walk through Fitzroy</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/31/fitzroy-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 22:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/31/fitzroy-walk/</guid>
      <description>For my birthday, Molly gave me a gift of a &amp;ldquo;Drinking History Tour&amp;rdquo; through Fitzroy, where I&amp;rsquo;ve been staying in Melbourne. On the evening of Halloween, I walked down to St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Cathedral to meet up with the tour. We learned some history &amp;amp; drank some drinks! It was pretty fun!
Fitzroy Street Library A house A Tribe Called Quest Judy Jetson St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Cathedral Everleigh, a dope cocktail bar George Costanza </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day at MONA</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/30/mona/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/30/mona/</guid>
      <description>I spent a day at the Museum of Old and New Art, known as &amp;ldquo;MONA&amp;rdquo;. It was an incredible experience, starting with a delightful ferry ride from Hobart up to the museum.
Spoilers below! If you want to see these works without knowledge of them, please skip this post.
James Turrell&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Unseen Seen + Weight of Darkness&amp;rdquo; broke my head. His work continues to blow me away since I first saw him at the Los Angeles Contemporary Museum of Art (LACMA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast before flying to Hobart</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/28/breakfast-and-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 14:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/28/breakfast-and-travel/</guid>
      <description>I had a wonderful breakfast at Industry Beans of Tea soaked steel cut oats, chia crumble, caramelised ginger foam, compressed watermelon, rosewater gel and fresh fruit. After, I flew to Hobart, Tasmania for a few days, which was awesome.
Breakfast at Industry Beans Espresso at Industry Beans Art Flying to Hobart</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keith Haring, Street Art, State Library of Victoria, a burger</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/27/art-state-library-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 20:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/27/art-state-library-burger/</guid>
      <description>I started off the day with a bagel at Mile End Bagels, which was a worthwhile look at what Australian bagels are. This one was good, if not a little off from what I&amp;rsquo;m used to otherwise. I saw a little art walking around Fitzroy and Collingwood, including a Keith Haring original!
I met up with Rob and his family at the Day of the Dead festival at Flagstaff Gardens in the afternoon, before Rob and I headed off onto a walking tour to see all that Melbourne has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grace Cafe, Aunty Peg&#39;s, Whisky &#43; Alement, Tonka</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/26/grace-auntypegs-whiskyalement-tonka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 22:09:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/26/grace-auntypegs-whiskyalement-tonka/</guid>
      <description>This morning, I had a scrumptious breakfast sandwich (the &amp;ldquo;Brekkie&amp;rdquo;) at Grace Cafe near my airbnb. Food and drink continue to amaze me in Melbourne in a way I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen so consistently well done across an entire city like this before. The eggs were light and fluffy and folded into a perfectly toasted ciabatta, with chives, cheese, sriracha mayo, onion jam.
I met up with Taylor at Aunty Peg&amp;rsquo;s. We enjoyed a coffee cupping before enjoying some coffees at the bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shandong Mama Mini, NGV, Ian Potter, Eau de Vie, Black Pearl, Capitano</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/25/shandong-ngv-cocktails/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 21:48:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/25/shandong-ngv-cocktails/</guid>
      <description>I had a lunch of &amp;ldquo;Dill-icious&amp;rdquo; pork dumplings and garlic cucumber salad with a homemade lemon iced tea at Shandong Mama Mini. I walked down to the National Gallery of Victoria (NGV) International to see the KAWS exhibit, along with a few other things in the permanent collection, before heading to the NGV Ian Potter museum focused on Australian art.
After the walking &amp;amp; the sight-seeing, I treated myself to some cocktails at Eau de Vie in the Central Business District and Black Pearl in Fitzroy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lune Croissanteri, Brunswick Street Alimentari, Groceries, &amp; Street art</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/24/lune-alimentari-groceries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 22:20:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/24/lune-alimentari-groceries/</guid>
      <description>I went to Lune Croissanteri for some pastries and coffee this morning, Brunswick Street Alimentari for lunch, and Rock Salt &amp;amp; Vinegar for dinner, before seeing some owl street art on my way home. I also survived my first trip to the grocery store today!
Lemon Curd Cruffin from Lune Croissanterie Ham and Gruyere Croissant from Lune Croissanterie The bakers at Lune Croissanterie Porchetta panini from Brunswick Street Alimentari I survived the grocery store!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sevens Seeds and Hosier Lane</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/23/seven-seeds-hosier-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/23/seven-seeds-hosier-lane/</guid>
      <description>I walked down to Carlton and had a delicious open lamb sandwich at Seven Seeds, before continuing my walk to Hosier Lane to see my dope street art. I also met up with Taylor &amp;amp; Maki for dinner!
Lamb sandwich at Seven Seeds Mark Zuckerberg is watching you Some shots from Hosier Lane Audrey</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
