<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tech on Tolar Town</title>
    <link>https://tolar.town/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tech on Tolar Town</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:10:10 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tolar.town/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Presidential Hopefuls: 2024 Edition</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2023/08/16/presidential-hopefuls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:10:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2023/08/16/presidential-hopefuls/</guid>
      <description>Tl;dr: I built a thing. Download it.
Next week is the first debate in this season of presidential hopefuls. The frontrunner has been indicted under dozens of counts in multiple jurisdictions. We could see multiple trials and maybe even multiple convictions between now and November 2024. We certainly will see many primaries, debates, gaffes, and scandals.
Which seems like the perfect time to launch the reboot of the successful 2020 era Presidential Hopefuls screensaver (for Mac!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2010: The days before the iPad</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2020/08/29/the-days-before-the-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 18:28:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2020/08/29/the-days-before-the-ipad/</guid>
      <description>January 27, 2010 Steve Jobs announced to the world a new product: the iPad. I had been the lead developer for a burgeoning motley crew of software developers learning on the job how to create iPhone apps at the storied magazine powerhouse Condé Nast. Our biggest success by far had been Epicurious, which allowed folks to find recipes on the go, build shopping lists, and then cook those recipes at home (RIP printers).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let a million screensavers bloom</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2020/04/13/screensavers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 17:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2020/04/13/screensavers/</guid>
      <description>This is nominally a &amp;ldquo;travel blog&amp;rdquo;, or something, but I also write code, and sometimes screensavers, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d try putting this out there to see how it goes. Let me know what you think! mail@tolar.town or on twitter @tolar.
Writing screensavers for macs is a little weird. But once you get past a few oddities, it can be lots of fun!
For purposes of this post, I assume you have some knowledge of and experience with Xcode and Swift.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
