<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>food on Tolar Town</title>
    <link>https://tolar.town/tags/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in food on Tolar Town</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 23:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tolar.town/tags/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PENGUINS!!!!</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/11/penguins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 23:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/11/penguins/</guid>
      <description>This afternoon and evening, I went to St Kilda Pier in the southern part of Melbourne. Every day at sunset, a colony of penguins swims back to the rocks to sleep. You can catch a couple of them inside the rocks during the day, but the real treat is right at sunset, when they swim up to the shore and waddle up to the rocks. PENGUINS!!!
St Kilda Pier</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Melbourne Market &amp; Supernormal</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/10/supernormal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 23:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/10/supernormal/</guid>
      <description>I met up with Taylor, Maki, Sheena, &amp;amp; Brenda at the South Melbourne Market, where we had coffee and pastries, walked around, did some shopping, and then had a paella lunch at Simply Spanish in the market.
We stopped by their house for a bit before Taylor &amp;amp; I went to dinner at Supernormal, which turned out to be my best meal in Melbourne (so far at least!). We started with cocktails and the raw Kingfish with mandarin dashi, arame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinner at Charcoal Lane</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/09/charcoal-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 21:19:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/09/charcoal-lane/</guid>
      <description>I stopped by Charcoal Lane tonight for dinner, which not only has delicious food and drink, but is also a &amp;ldquo;social enterprise restaurant that provides guidance and opportunity to young Aboriginal people who are in need of a fresh start in life.&amp;rdquo; So you can feel good about where your money&amp;rsquo;s going while enjoying some kangaroo!
I started with a negroni: Native pepperberry infused gin, Antica Formula, Campari. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t quite detect any significant pepperberry flavor, but it was still delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day in Torquay and a drive to see some animals</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/07/torquay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 18:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/07/torquay/</guid>
      <description>I spent the morning in Torquay with Rob. We had breakfast at Ginger Monkey, where I had a scrumptious mushroom and poached eggs on toast, and we took a tour of the Surf Museum. He went home to work, and I drove down to Anglesea to a golf club where kangaroos live. I then drove further down the Great Ocean Road, which was quite gorgeous. If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t raining, I would have stopped to take some photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne to Torquay</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/06/melbourne-to-torquay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 22:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/06/melbourne-to-torquay/</guid>
      <description>I rented (or &amp;ldquo;hired&amp;rdquo;) a car via Oyo, which is like Zipcar, but is somehow related to Toyota (get it, &amp;ldquo;Toyota&amp;rdquo;), and I drove down to Torquay, a beautiful town on the beach about a 90 minute drive from Melbourne. I saw some lovely beaches, some gorgeous rolling hills, had some good food, and experienced some mediocre fast food. Plus I got to hang out with Rob and his family!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to the Victorian Parliament</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/04/parliament/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 22:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/04/parliament/</guid>
      <description>I had a lovely breakfast at Rustica in Fitzroy, followed by a late morning espresso at Aunty Peg&amp;rsquo;s. I walked around a bit in Fitzroy and had a mid-afternoon visit to the Victorian House of Parliament, which was pretty neat. I got to see where Queen Elizabeth sat to open Parliament back in 1954!
I had a delicious dinner of dumplings &amp;amp; chicken at Hutong Dumpling House and a couple of cocktails at Bar Americano and Over Board, which were dope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A trip to Hawthorne</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/03/hawthorne/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 20:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/03/hawthorne/</guid>
      <description>I traveled to Hawthorne via a tram and a train to Taylor&amp;rsquo;s house to visit him, Maki, their child Sheena, and Taylor&amp;rsquo;s mom Brenda. It&amp;rsquo;s been great to catch up, and I loved meeting the baby!
Taylor &amp;amp; Sheena 
Sheena &amp;amp; I 
Hawthorne views 
Breakfast in Fitzroy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day out shopping</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/02/shopping-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 20:12:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/02/shopping-day/</guid>
      <description>It was a slow morning due to quite a bit of ongoing rain outside. I did make it out in the morning all the way across the street to the Saturday market to buy a loaf of sourdough and a coffee (which I then had with some eggs I made at home). I finally left the house for a bit this afternoon to get some lunch and check out some shops that were on my list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A lazy day in Fitzroy</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/01/lazy-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 14:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/01/lazy-day/</guid>
      <description>I was wiped out from traveling back from Tasmania and doing the walking tour last night, so I laid low around the neighborhood, did some laundry, and ordered in for dinner. (And got this blog updated!)
Espresso, Grace Café 
Mushrooms on toast, Grace Café 
Brunswick Street building 
Fried chicken sandwich, Industry Beans</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last day in Hobart</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/31/last-day-in-hobart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 14:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/31/last-day-in-hobart/</guid>
      <description>I walked around Hobart a bit before heading back to Melbourne. Halloween isn&amp;rsquo;t huge in Australia, but I did see a few costumes … maybe?
Baked eggs 
Port 
Halloween? 
Wildlife 
I thought I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get my chance, but the Hobart airport came through, and I had a scallop pie for lunch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evening in Hobart</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/30/evening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 21:30:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/30/evening/</guid>
      <description>I met up with Joel, met his adorable St. Bernard named Victoria, then we got some dinner and some whisky to finish off the night.
Victoria 
Gnocchi with funghi sauce 
Pizza 
Port at sunset 
Glass House bathroom selfie</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day at MONA</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/30/mona/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/30/mona/</guid>
      <description>I spent a day at the Museum of Old and New Art, known as &amp;ldquo;MONA&amp;rdquo;. It was an incredible experience, starting with a delightful ferry ride from Hobart up to the museum.
Spoilers below! If you want to see these works without knowledge of them, please skip this post.
James Turrell&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Unseen Seen + Weight of Darkness&amp;rdquo; broke my head. His work continues to blow me away since I first saw him at the Los Angeles Contemporary Museum of Art (LACMA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pennicott seafood seduction cruise</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/29/pennicott-seafood-cruise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 15:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/29/pennicott-seafood-cruise/</guid>
      <description>Per Harper&amp;rsquo;s recommendation, I went on the Pennicott Seafood Seduction tour today, where our fearless guides Sam &amp;amp; Hugh took us on a cruise through the waters of Hobart, Tasmania. Not only were they our guides, they were also our captains, fishermen, chefs, and entertainers – their constant prattle &amp;amp; wit back and forth kept the cruise light-hearted and fun. The day was amazing, the food top-notch, and the sights were something to behold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobart is pretty dope</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/29/hobart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 09:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/29/hobart/</guid>
      <description>I spent a few days in Hobart, Tasmania. This first day, I checked into the fabulous Macq Hotel, met up with Harper&amp;rsquo;s friends Joel &amp;amp; Mustafa, and drank some delicious local gin &amp;amp; whisky.
Mustafa and Joel 
Macq Hotel 
Hartshorn Sheep Whey gin 
Potato, onion, &amp;amp; leek frittata, from The Old Wharf in the Macq Hotel 
Selfie 
Port 
Ferry to MONA 
Macq hotel with cruise ship</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast before flying to Hobart</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/28/breakfast-and-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 14:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/28/breakfast-and-travel/</guid>
      <description>I had a wonderful breakfast at Industry Beans of Tea soaked steel cut oats, chia crumble, caramelised ginger foam, compressed watermelon, rosewater gel and fresh fruit. After, I flew to Hobart, Tasmania for a few days, which was awesome.
Breakfast at Industry Beans 
Espresso at Industry Beans 
Art 
Flying to Hobart</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keith Haring, Street Art, State Library of Victoria, a burger</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/27/art-state-library-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 20:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/27/art-state-library-burger/</guid>
      <description>I started off the day with a bagel at Mile End Bagels, which was a worthwhile look at what Australian bagels are. This one was good, if not a little off from what I&amp;rsquo;m used to otherwise. I saw a little art walking around Fitzroy and Collingwood, including a Keith Haring original!
I met up with Rob and his family at the Day of the Dead festival at Flagstaff Gardens in the afternoon, before Rob and I headed off onto a walking tour to see all that Melbourne has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grace Cafe, Aunty Peg&#39;s, Whisky &#43; Alement, Tonka</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/26/grace-auntypegs-whiskyalement-tonka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 22:09:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/26/grace-auntypegs-whiskyalement-tonka/</guid>
      <description>This morning, I had a scrumptious breakfast sandwich (the &amp;ldquo;Brekkie&amp;rdquo;) at Grace Cafe near my airbnb. Food and drink continue to amaze me in Melbourne in a way I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen so consistently well done across an entire city like this before. The eggs were light and fluffy and folded into a perfectly toasted ciabatta, with chives, cheese, sriracha mayo, onion jam.
I met up with Taylor at Aunty Peg&amp;rsquo;s. We enjoyed a coffee cupping before enjoying some coffees at the bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shandong Mama Mini, NGV, Ian Potter, Eau de Vie, Black Pearl, Capitano</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/25/shandong-ngv-cocktails/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 21:48:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/25/shandong-ngv-cocktails/</guid>
      <description>I had a lunch of &amp;ldquo;Dill-icious&amp;rdquo; pork dumplings and garlic cucumber salad with a homemade lemon iced tea at Shandong Mama Mini. I walked down to the National Gallery of Victoria (NGV) International to see the KAWS exhibit, along with a few other things in the permanent collection, before heading to the NGV Ian Potter museum focused on Australian art.
After the walking &amp;amp; the sight-seeing, I treated myself to some cocktails at Eau de Vie in the Central Business District and Black Pearl in Fitzroy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lune Croissanteri, Brunswick Street Alimentari, Groceries, &amp; Street art</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/24/lune-alimentari-groceries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 22:20:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/24/lune-alimentari-groceries/</guid>
      <description>I went to Lune Croissanteri for some pastries and coffee this morning, Brunswick Street Alimentari for lunch, and Rock Salt &amp;amp; Vinegar for dinner, before seeing some owl street art on my way home. I also survived my first trip to the grocery store today!
Lemon Curd Cruffin from Lune Croissanterie 
Ham and Gruyere Croissant from Lune Croissanterie 
The bakers at Lune Croissanterie 
Porchetta panini from Brunswick Street Alimentari</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sevens Seeds and Hosier Lane</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/23/seven-seeds-hosier-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/23/seven-seeds-hosier-lane/</guid>
      <description>I walked down to Carlton and had a delicious open lamb sandwich at Seven Seeds, before continuing my walk to Hosier Lane to see my dope street art. I also met up with Taylor &amp;amp; Maki for dinner!
Lamb sandwich at Seven Seeds 
Mark Zuckerberg is watching you 
Some shots from Hosier Lane 
Audrey</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast at Industry Beans</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/23/breakfast-at-industry-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 11:45:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/23/breakfast-at-industry-beans/</guid>
      <description>My first morning in Melbourne! I walked across the street to Industry Beans, where I had a wonderful breakfast in a beautiful sun-drenched restaurant.
Flat white 
Smoked Manchego Omelette: &amp;ldquo;Chilli roasted zucchini, pickled sweet fennel, paprika roasted pumpkin seeds and pumpkin sourdough&amp;rdquo; 
The interior at Industry Beans</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>