<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tolar Town</title>
    <link>https://tolar.town/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tolar Town</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 22:08:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tolar.town/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2 museums &amp; some food</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/20/seoul-museums/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 22:08:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/20/seoul-museums/</guid>
      <description>My first full day in Seoul! I had a good breakfast at Bimbam Cafe near the hotel, then walked down to the War Memorial of Korea, which encompassed lots of history of Korea, with an emphasis on the Korean War.
I had a yummy sandwich at Casablanca in Itaewon, then met up with Tiffany &amp;amp; fam to see the Gyeongbokgung Palace and the Arario museum.
We had a dope Korean dinner of seafood &amp;amp; veggie pancake, a spicy salad with chestnut jelly, and a creamy noodle soup, along with makgeolli, a Korean rice wine that was yum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul!</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/19/seoul/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/19/seoul/</guid>
      <description>After a long flight from Melbourne with a middle-of-the-night layover in Singapore, I made it to Seoul! I took the KAL (Korean Airlines) Limousine Bus from Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Incheon airport to the Grand Hyatt hotel. The bus was pretty nice, as it does a loop from the airport to major hotels in Seoul, so it&amp;rsquo;s a easy, inexpensive way to efficiently get to the destination.
I was pretty wiped out when I checked in, but I managed to walk down to Full Moon where I had a beef bulgogi meal, complete with various Korean style sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So long, Australia</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/18/so-long-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 22:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/18/so-long-australia/</guid>
      <description>For the past four weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been in Australia, mostly staying in Melbourne, but also Torquay and Hobart (Tasmania). It&amp;rsquo;s been amazing! I&amp;rsquo;ve been blown away by how nice of a city is, let alone the fantastic food, coffee, &amp;amp; drinks available nearly everywhere.
Here are a few terms I&amp;rsquo;ve learned along the way…
   Australian English US English     Footy Australia-rules football   Toasties toasted sandwich   Jaffle also a toasted sandwich   Take away take out   Booking reservation   Return round trip   Brekkie breakfast   burger literally anything in a bun (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Johnston street festival</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/17/street-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/17/street-festival/</guid>
      <description>Just a few blocks from where I&amp;rsquo;m staying, I happened upon a multi-block street festival that had two stages of various music &amp;amp; dancing, and in between a menagerie of food options. I ended up getting some chicken &amp;lsquo;wanton&amp;rsquo; tacos, which were pretty tasty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mate Fest</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/16/mate-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 23:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/16/mate-fest/</guid>
      <description>Today, Taylor &amp;amp; I went to Mate Fest, an international beer fest hosted by Moon Dog Brewery in Melbourne. Our friend Erik from Magpie in Seoul gave a masterclass, which was pretty fun!
Breakfast at Grace Cafe: Chilli Scrambled Eggs, with Lao gan ma chilli, pickled shiitake, enoki and szechuan crunch on toast 
Taylor &amp;amp; me 
Magpie&amp;rsquo;s Erik giving a masterclass 
Moon dog had a dope analog style version of Pong</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A random day</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/14/random/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 23:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/14/random/</guid>
      <description>A mostly random sort of day with Erik and Taylor. We ate and drank our way around Melbourne.
Soft shelled crab &amp;lsquo;burger&amp;rsquo;, from Proud Mary&amp;rsquo;s. (basically, they seem to call anything on a bun a &amp;lsquo;burger&amp;rsquo;) 
Tempura green beans, from Byrdi. 
Grau Projekt: an art opening that a bartender told me about, which had about 8 pieces on the wall, literal tons of salt on the floor, and maybe 9 people there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low key day</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/13/lowkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/13/lowkey/</guid>
      <description>I mostly had a low-key day before meeting up with Rob and Erik for a fantastic dinner at Chin Chin, then Erik &amp;amp; I went to Mr West for some beer.
Earlier in the day, I stopped by my artwork to discover only half of it had been painted over in its first 24 hours of life, which I was pretty happy about! (I mostly expected it to be completely gone by then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street art</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/12/street-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 14:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/12/street-art/</guid>
      <description>I went on a walking tour of street art in Melbourne that I found on Airbnb. Lukas took me and another guest around to see some cool street art, pointed out various different styles, and put it all into context and the culture around the street art scene here. BUT, the highlight is that we got to make our own street art. It was awesome! I was super nervous to start, but it came out way better than I had hoped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PENGUINS!!!!</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/11/penguins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 23:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/11/penguins/</guid>
      <description>This afternoon and evening, I went to St Kilda Pier in the southern part of Melbourne. Every day at sunset, a colony of penguins swims back to the rocks to sleep. You can catch a couple of them inside the rocks during the day, but the real treat is right at sunset, when they swim up to the shore and waddle up to the rocks. PENGUINS!!!
St Kilda Pier</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Melbourne Zoo</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/11/melbourne-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 13:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/11/melbourne-zoo/</guid>
      <description>After a lot of colder, rainy days, it was gorgeous in Melbourne today. I walked a couple of miles over to the zoo, where I saw some dope animals.
Elephant 
Giraffe 
Wild dogs 
Lion</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Melbourne Market &amp; Supernormal</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/10/supernormal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 23:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/10/supernormal/</guid>
      <description>I met up with Taylor, Maki, Sheena, &amp;amp; Brenda at the South Melbourne Market, where we had coffee and pastries, walked around, did some shopping, and then had a paella lunch at Simply Spanish in the market.
We stopped by their house for a bit before Taylor &amp;amp; I went to dinner at Supernormal, which turned out to be my best meal in Melbourne (so far at least!). We started with cocktails and the raw Kingfish with mandarin dashi, arame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinner at Charcoal Lane</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/09/charcoal-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 21:19:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/09/charcoal-lane/</guid>
      <description>I stopped by Charcoal Lane tonight for dinner, which not only has delicious food and drink, but is also a &amp;ldquo;social enterprise restaurant that provides guidance and opportunity to young Aboriginal people who are in need of a fresh start in life.&amp;rdquo; So you can feel good about where your money&amp;rsquo;s going while enjoying some kangaroo!
I started with a negroni: Native pepperberry infused gin, Antica Formula, Campari. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t quite detect any significant pepperberry flavor, but it was still delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day in Torquay and a drive to see some animals</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/07/torquay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 18:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/07/torquay/</guid>
      <description>I spent the morning in Torquay with Rob. We had breakfast at Ginger Monkey, where I had a scrumptious mushroom and poached eggs on toast, and we took a tour of the Surf Museum. He went home to work, and I drove down to Anglesea to a golf club where kangaroos live. I then drove further down the Great Ocean Road, which was quite gorgeous. If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t raining, I would have stopped to take some photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne to Torquay</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/06/melbourne-to-torquay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 22:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/06/melbourne-to-torquay/</guid>
      <description>I rented (or &amp;ldquo;hired&amp;rdquo;) a car via Oyo, which is like Zipcar, but is somehow related to Toyota (get it, &amp;ldquo;Toyota&amp;rdquo;), and I drove down to Torquay, a beautiful town on the beach about a 90 minute drive from Melbourne. I saw some lovely beaches, some gorgeous rolling hills, had some good food, and experienced some mediocre fast food. Plus I got to hang out with Rob and his family!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to the Royal Botanic Gardens</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/05/royal-botanic-gardens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 14:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/05/royal-botanic-gardens/</guid>
      <description>Taylor, Sheena, &amp;amp; I took a walk around the Royal Botanic Gardens in Victoria, which was gorgeous. We had a coffee at the tea room in the middle of the gardens, and later had a delightful lunch a short walk away at Denis the Menace (lol).
Taylor &amp;amp; Sheena 
Gardens 
Sheena &amp;amp; Taylor 
Spaghetti</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A visit to the Victorian Parliament</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/04/parliament/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 22:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/04/parliament/</guid>
      <description>I had a lovely breakfast at Rustica in Fitzroy, followed by a late morning espresso at Aunty Peg&amp;rsquo;s. I walked around a bit in Fitzroy and had a mid-afternoon visit to the Victorian House of Parliament, which was pretty neat. I got to see where Queen Elizabeth sat to open Parliament back in 1954!
I had a delicious dinner of dumplings &amp;amp; chicken at Hutong Dumpling House and a couple of cocktails at Bar Americano and Over Board, which were dope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A trip to Hawthorne</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/03/hawthorne/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 20:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/03/hawthorne/</guid>
      <description>I traveled to Hawthorne via a tram and a train to Taylor&amp;rsquo;s house to visit him, Maki, their child Sheena, and Taylor&amp;rsquo;s mom Brenda. It&amp;rsquo;s been great to catch up, and I loved meeting the baby!
Taylor &amp;amp; Sheena 
Sheena &amp;amp; I 
Hawthorne views 
Breakfast in Fitzroy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day out shopping</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/02/shopping-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 20:12:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/02/shopping-day/</guid>
      <description>It was a slow morning due to quite a bit of ongoing rain outside. I did make it out in the morning all the way across the street to the Saturday market to buy a loaf of sourdough and a coffee (which I then had with some eggs I made at home). I finally left the house for a bit this afternoon to get some lunch and check out some shops that were on my list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The last few days: Tasmania!</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/01/wrap-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 20:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/01/wrap-up/</guid>
      <description>I spent the last few days in Tasmania, but I left my laptop behind, so I&amp;rsquo;ve just posted photos from the trip. Here are the posts I&amp;rsquo;ve just posted:
 Breakfast before flying to Hobart Hobart is pretty dope Pennicott seafood seduction cruise A day at MONA Evening in Hobart Last day in Hobart A walk through Fitzroy A lazy day  Come to Tasmania, we mean you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A lazy day in Fitzroy</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/01/lazy-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 14:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/11/01/lazy-day/</guid>
      <description>I was wiped out from traveling back from Tasmania and doing the walking tour last night, so I laid low around the neighborhood, did some laundry, and ordered in for dinner. (And got this blog updated!)
Espresso, Grace Café 
Mushrooms on toast, Grace Café 
Brunswick Street building 
Fried chicken sandwich, Industry Beans</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A walk through Fitzroy</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/31/fitzroy-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 22:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/31/fitzroy-walk/</guid>
      <description>For my birthday, Molly gave me a gift of a &amp;ldquo;Drinking History Tour&amp;rdquo; through Fitzroy, where I&amp;rsquo;ve been staying in Melbourne. On the evening of Halloween, I walked down to St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Cathedral to meet up with the tour. We learned some history &amp;amp; drank some drinks! It was pretty fun!
Fitzroy Street Library 
A house 
A Tribe Called Quest 
Judy Jetson 
St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Cathedral</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last day in Hobart</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/31/last-day-in-hobart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 14:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/31/last-day-in-hobart/</guid>
      <description>I walked around Hobart a bit before heading back to Melbourne. Halloween isn&amp;rsquo;t huge in Australia, but I did see a few costumes … maybe?
Baked eggs 
Port 
Halloween? 
Wildlife 
I thought I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get my chance, but the Hobart airport came through, and I had a scallop pie for lunch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evening in Hobart</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/30/evening/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 21:30:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/30/evening/</guid>
      <description>I met up with Joel, met his adorable St. Bernard named Victoria, then we got some dinner and some whisky to finish off the night.
Victoria 
Gnocchi with funghi sauce 
Pizza 
Port at sunset 
Glass House bathroom selfie</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day at MONA</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/30/mona/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/30/mona/</guid>
      <description>I spent a day at the Museum of Old and New Art, known as &amp;ldquo;MONA&amp;rdquo;. It was an incredible experience, starting with a delightful ferry ride from Hobart up to the museum.
Spoilers below! If you want to see these works without knowledge of them, please skip this post.
James Turrell&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Unseen Seen + Weight of Darkness&amp;rdquo; broke my head. His work continues to blow me away since I first saw him at the Los Angeles Contemporary Museum of Art (LACMA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pennicott seafood seduction cruise</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/29/pennicott-seafood-cruise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 15:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/29/pennicott-seafood-cruise/</guid>
      <description>Per Harper&amp;rsquo;s recommendation, I went on the Pennicott Seafood Seduction tour today, where our fearless guides Sam &amp;amp; Hugh took us on a cruise through the waters of Hobart, Tasmania. Not only were they our guides, they were also our captains, fishermen, chefs, and entertainers – their constant prattle &amp;amp; wit back and forth kept the cruise light-hearted and fun. The day was amazing, the food top-notch, and the sights were something to behold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobart is pretty dope</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/29/hobart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 09:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/29/hobart/</guid>
      <description>I spent a few days in Hobart, Tasmania. This first day, I checked into the fabulous Macq Hotel, met up with Harper&amp;rsquo;s friends Joel &amp;amp; Mustafa, and drank some delicious local gin &amp;amp; whisky.
Mustafa and Joel 
Macq Hotel 
Hartshorn Sheep Whey gin 
Potato, onion, &amp;amp; leek frittata, from The Old Wharf in the Macq Hotel 
Selfie 
Port 
Ferry to MONA 
Macq hotel with cruise ship</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast before flying to Hobart</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/28/breakfast-and-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 14:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/28/breakfast-and-travel/</guid>
      <description>I had a wonderful breakfast at Industry Beans of Tea soaked steel cut oats, chia crumble, caramelised ginger foam, compressed watermelon, rosewater gel and fresh fruit. After, I flew to Hobart, Tasmania for a few days, which was awesome.
Breakfast at Industry Beans 
Espresso at Industry Beans 
Art 
Flying to Hobart</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keith Haring, Street Art, State Library of Victoria, a burger</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/27/art-state-library-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 20:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/27/art-state-library-burger/</guid>
      <description>I started off the day with a bagel at Mile End Bagels, which was a worthwhile look at what Australian bagels are. This one was good, if not a little off from what I&amp;rsquo;m used to otherwise. I saw a little art walking around Fitzroy and Collingwood, including a Keith Haring original!
I met up with Rob and his family at the Day of the Dead festival at Flagstaff Gardens in the afternoon, before Rob and I headed off onto a walking tour to see all that Melbourne has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grace Cafe, Aunty Peg&#39;s, Whisky &#43; Alement, Tonka</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/26/grace-auntypegs-whiskyalement-tonka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 22:09:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/26/grace-auntypegs-whiskyalement-tonka/</guid>
      <description>This morning, I had a scrumptious breakfast sandwich (the &amp;ldquo;Brekkie&amp;rdquo;) at Grace Cafe near my airbnb. Food and drink continue to amaze me in Melbourne in a way I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen so consistently well done across an entire city like this before. The eggs were light and fluffy and folded into a perfectly toasted ciabatta, with chives, cheese, sriracha mayo, onion jam.
I met up with Taylor at Aunty Peg&amp;rsquo;s. We enjoyed a coffee cupping before enjoying some coffees at the bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shandong Mama Mini, NGV, Ian Potter, Eau de Vie, Black Pearl, Capitano</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/25/shandong-ngv-cocktails/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 21:48:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/25/shandong-ngv-cocktails/</guid>
      <description>I had a lunch of &amp;ldquo;Dill-icious&amp;rdquo; pork dumplings and garlic cucumber salad with a homemade lemon iced tea at Shandong Mama Mini. I walked down to the National Gallery of Victoria (NGV) International to see the KAWS exhibit, along with a few other things in the permanent collection, before heading to the NGV Ian Potter museum focused on Australian art.
After the walking &amp;amp; the sight-seeing, I treated myself to some cocktails at Eau de Vie in the Central Business District and Black Pearl in Fitzroy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lune Croissanteri, Brunswick Street Alimentari, Groceries, &amp; Street art</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/24/lune-alimentari-groceries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 22:20:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/24/lune-alimentari-groceries/</guid>
      <description>I went to Lune Croissanteri for some pastries and coffee this morning, Brunswick Street Alimentari for lunch, and Rock Salt &amp;amp; Vinegar for dinner, before seeing some owl street art on my way home. I also survived my first trip to the grocery store today!
Lemon Curd Cruffin from Lune Croissanterie 
Ham and Gruyere Croissant from Lune Croissanterie 
The bakers at Lune Croissanterie 
Porchetta panini from Brunswick Street Alimentari</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sevens Seeds and Hosier Lane</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/23/seven-seeds-hosier-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/23/seven-seeds-hosier-lane/</guid>
      <description>I walked down to Carlton and had a delicious open lamb sandwich at Seven Seeds, before continuing my walk to Hosier Lane to see my dope street art. I also met up with Taylor &amp;amp; Maki for dinner!
Lamb sandwich at Seven Seeds 
Mark Zuckerberg is watching you 
Some shots from Hosier Lane 
Audrey</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast at Industry Beans</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/23/breakfast-at-industry-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 11:45:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/23/breakfast-at-industry-beans/</guid>
      <description>My first morning in Melbourne! I walked across the street to Industry Beans, where I had a wonderful breakfast in a beautiful sun-drenched restaurant.
Flat white 
Smoked Manchego Omelette: &amp;ldquo;Chilli roasted zucchini, pickled sweet fennel, paprika roasted pumpkin seeds and pumpkin sourdough&amp;rdquo; 
The interior at Industry Beans</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A walk around Fitzroy</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/22/fitzroy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 19:38:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/22/fitzroy/</guid>
      <description>In order to stave off impending jet lag, I walked around the neighborhood on this beautiful Spring day.
Edinburgh Gardens 
&amp;ldquo;The Unsung Hero&amp;rdquo; (2019), by Kathy Holowko 
Fitzroy Nolij 
Fitzroy art 
Baby on top of a building in Fitzroy 
Fitzroy animal house</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traveling from Vallejo to Melbourne</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/22/travel-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 13:15:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/22/travel-day/</guid>
      <description>Starting Sunday afternoon California time, I took a Lyft from Vallejo to Sacramento airport, where I endured a 5 hour delay in taking off. We made it to Los Angeles, just in time for me to sprint across two terminals and take a shuttle bus to make it for my next leg from LA to Sydney. Delta&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Premium Select&amp;rdquo; was very comfortable with a fairly large TV screen, good food &amp;amp; wine, and quality service from our flight attendants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wine tasting in Sonoma</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/18/sonoma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 21:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/18/sonoma/</guid>
      <description>Adam, Tara, &amp;amp; I drove from Vallejo up through the greater Sonoma region and Russian River Valley to visit a few wineries: Moshin, VJB, and Domaine Carneros. Later, Adam &amp;amp; I made a brief trip into San Francisco to attend a sound bath, complete with gongs and flutes. The wine was great, while the sound bath was a bit odd (and I probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t return any time soon). But we at least got a solid hamburger in at a diner afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A lazy day in Vallejo</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/17/vallejo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/17/vallejo/</guid>
      <description>A lazy day in Vallejo, California, hanging out with Adam &amp;amp; Peter&amp;rsquo;s dogs &amp;amp; pig.
Chich 
Uta 
Ita 
Backyard</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving NYC</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/16/departing-nyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/16/departing-nyc/</guid>
      <description>I checked out from the TWA hotel and took off from NYC, off to California for a few days!
Checking out of the TWA hotel 
Delta airplane to California</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A night at the TWA Hotel</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/15/twa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 22:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/15/twa/</guid>
      <description>Before leaving town, I spent the night at the new TWA Hotel at JFK airport, where I enjoyed the Sunken Bar &amp;amp; the Connie bar, which is pretty neat in that it&amp;rsquo;s inside an actual vintage airplane.
A hallway at TWA 
The Sunken Bar 
Martini at the Sunken Bar 
The outside of the Connie bar 
The airstrip outside the hotel. 
Inside the Connie bar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last day in Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/15/last-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 16:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/15/last-day/</guid>
      <description>Today, I had lunch at Allswell in Williamsburg, and then walked up to see the Kaws sculpture in Greenpoint, before heading over to Manhattan to pick up some currency ahead of my trip.
Allswell, Williamsburg 
the kaws sculpture</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Union Square Cafe</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/14/union-square-cafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 19:47:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/14/union-square-cafe/</guid>
      <description>Today, I had lunch at one of my favorite spots, Union Square Cafe. Beforehand, I walked past the New York City Columbus Day Parade, and took a few photos.
union square cafe 
a marching band at the parade 
a float getting ready for the parade</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day in Manhattan</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/12/manhattan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 17:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/12/manhattan/</guid>
      <description>Today, I had brunch at Momofuku Ssäm Bar with some friends, walked down to Soho to the REI store to buy a new jacket for my travels, and then I walked home across the Williamsburg Bridge.
espresso from saltwater 
the bar at momofuku ssäm bar 
ham &amp;amp; bacon cornbread &amp;amp; burrata, with benton&amp;rsquo;s ham &amp;amp; bacon and pickled chilis, from momofuku ssäm bar 
brunch at momofuku ssäm bar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funemployment: Day Five</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/11/day-five/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 22:55:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/11/day-five/</guid>
      <description>I survived the week!
Soundview Royale from the dutch 
Nori Fries from katana kitten 
charlie brown in front of the ups warehouse 
post-haircut selfie 
Bright and Sunny from katana kitten 
paul</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funemployment: Day Four</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/10/day-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 21:31:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/10/day-four/</guid>
      <description>times square 
my aunt, mary davis holt, speaking at nasdaq 
me</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funemployment: Day Three</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/09/day-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 21:16:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/09/day-three/</guid>
      <description>brisket sandwich from hometown bbq in red hook (brooklyn) 
clint in front of a wall of flowers in red hook (brooklyn) 
bottle topper at katana kitten in west village (manhattan) 
mortadella tonkatsu sando at katana kitten in west village (manhattan)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funemployment: Day Two</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/08/day-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 13:50:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/08/day-two/</guid>
      <description>the east river from east river state park in williamsburg (brooklyn) 
espresso at cafe beit in williamsburg (brooklyn) 
me! 
nyc transit station</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funemployment: Day One</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/07/day-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 15:57:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/07/day-one/</guid>
      <description>me! 
men getting on a bus in williamsburg (brooklyn)
mist art in domino park in williamsburg (brooklyn) 
anna art 
rando art</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New beginnings</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/04/new-beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 17:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/04/new-beginnings/</guid>
      <description>Today, after 5&amp;frac12; year across Modest, PayPal, Braintree, &amp;amp; Venmo, I have turned in my laptop &amp;amp; corporate phone. What&amp;rsquo;s next? Time to travel! I&amp;rsquo;ll be keeping this blog updated as I go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dino Tolar</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/09/29/dino-tolar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 12:38:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/09/29/dino-tolar/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More to come…</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/09/29/more-to-come/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 11:20:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/09/29/more-to-come/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, y&#39;all</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/09/29/hey-yall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 11:19:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/09/29/hey-yall/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>