<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cocktails on Tolar Town</title>
    <link>https://tolar.town/tags/cocktails/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cocktails on Tolar Town</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 09:00:06 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tolar.town/tags/cocktails/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans: bars</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2020/01/27/dranks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 09:00:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2020/01/27/dranks/</guid>
      <description>Me in the dungeon 
Adam 
Adam &amp;amp; Peter 
Amaro flight at Gianna&amp;rsquo;s 
A wedding party crashed our quiet cocktail hour at Jewel of the South.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grace Cafe, Aunty Peg&#39;s, Whisky &#43; Alement, Tonka</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/26/grace-auntypegs-whiskyalement-tonka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 22:09:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/26/grace-auntypegs-whiskyalement-tonka/</guid>
      <description>This morning, I had a scrumptious breakfast sandwich (the &amp;ldquo;Brekkie&amp;rdquo;) at Grace Cafe near my airbnb. Food and drink continue to amaze me in Melbourne in a way I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen so consistently well done across an entire city like this before. The eggs were light and fluffy and folded into a perfectly toasted ciabatta, with chives, cheese, sriracha mayo, onion jam.
I met up with Taylor at Aunty Peg&amp;rsquo;s. We enjoyed a coffee cupping before enjoying some coffees at the bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shandong Mama Mini, NGV, Ian Potter, Eau de Vie, Black Pearl, Capitano</title>
      <link>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/25/shandong-ngv-cocktails/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 21:48:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tolar.town/posts/2019/10/25/shandong-ngv-cocktails/</guid>
      <description>I had a lunch of &amp;ldquo;Dill-icious&amp;rdquo; pork dumplings and garlic cucumber salad with a homemade lemon iced tea at Shandong Mama Mini. I walked down to the National Gallery of Victoria (NGV) International to see the KAWS exhibit, along with a few other things in the permanent collection, before heading to the NGV Ian Potter museum focused on Australian art.
After the walking &amp;amp; the sight-seeing, I treated myself to some cocktails at Eau de Vie in the Central Business District and Black Pearl in Fitzroy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>